Whoa, I was about to get flattened...
(ナルト)ふぅ…
危なく ペシャンコだったぜ。
(フウカ)フフフフ… フエンの仕掛けも
たいしたことがないねぇ。
Fuen's traps are nothing special.
(地陸)これほどの使い手とは…。
I can't believe they're this skilled.
くっ！
もはや 我が手には負えぬか…。
I can't handle him anymore.
(フドウ)うぉ～っ!!
(ヤマト)やったか!?
Did I get him?
フフフフフ…。
効かん！
That won't work!
この！
Damn you!
It's futile!
ムダだ！
ちょこまかと…。
Scurrying about like that...
Earth Style! Stone Plate Coffin.
土遁 岩板柩！
終わったな。
It's over.
フン！ 墓標くらい建ててやるか。
I guess I can at least make him
a grave marker.
フフフフフ…。
チッ！ フエンの野郎のおかげで
汗 かいちまった。
I had to work up a sweat
on account of that jerk Fuen.
フッ… 自分の術を
過信しすぎなんだよ。
You place too much confidence
in your own Jutsu.
とどめの確認は
ちゃんとしないとね。
You have to make sure
you've finished the job.
《しかし… ヤツらの狙いはなんだ？
But what are they after?
遺体を盗み出したうえに
わざと目立つように逃げた…》
After stealing the bodies,
they intentionally attract
attention in their escape...
Are they after one of us
from the Leaf?
狙いは
ボクら 木ノ葉のうちの誰か？
If so, is Danzo involved?
とすると ダンゾウがらみか？
habataitara
Once I fly,
modorena ito itte
I won't be coming back, I said.
mezashita no wa
And I set out.
aoi aoi ano sora
For that blue, blue sky.
kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
I haven't learned "sadness" yet.
setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
And I'm just starting to grasp "misery".
anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
Even this feeling I hold towards you.
ima kotoba ni wakatteku
Is now turning into "words".
michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
Waking up from the dream of this unknown world.
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
I spread these wings and fly.
habataitara
Once I fly,
modorena ito itte
I won't be coming back, I said.
mezashita no wa
And I set out.
aoi aoi ano sora
For that blue, blue sky.
tsuki nuketara
Knowing I'll find the answer,
mitsukaru to shitte
If I pierce through it.
furikiru hodo
if I break free,
aoi aoi ano sora
From that blue, blue sky.
Impermanence
(サクラ)ふぅ… 敵の術中に
完全に はまったみたいね。
It appears we totally got caught
in the enemy's Jutsu.
(サクラ)まず みんなと合流しないと。
First, we must join up with the others.
きっと どこか 近くに
避難してるんだと…。
I bet they evacuated to
some nearby location.
Huh?!
えっ？
(ソラ)罰当たり野郎 捜してくらぁ。
I'm off to find that awful jerk.
Just a minute!
ちょ… 待ちなさい！
There's no point to looking together.
(ソラ)一緒に捜してても
しかたねえからさ！
ったく… 結局 全員
バラバラになっちゃったじゃない。
For crying out loud.
So in the end,
everyone's scattered all over...
はぁ…。
(サクラ)しかたないか。
I guess it can't be helped.
It's not like he received
any training on teamwork.
チームプレーの訓練を
受けてるわけじゃないだろうし。
Come to think of it,
didn't Naruto flunk that part?
そういえば
ナルトも赤点だったっけ。
What's the deal with her?!
なんだ アイツ？
(フウカ)あ～あ やだやだ 肉体労働。
Oh, boy. I hate... manual labor...
(フウカ)手間ヒマかけず 仕掛けに
任せるつもりだったのにさ。
And here the plan was to
let the traps do the work
without me having to get involved.
しようがないね…
ちゃっちゃと やっちゃおうか！
I guess I have no choice.
I'll take care of this.
フン… ちゃっちゃと
終わりにしてやらぁ！
I'll end this lickety-split!
いくぜ！
Let's go!
え～っ!?
What?!
お前 いきなり何すんだよ!?
What the hell are you doing
out of the blue like that?
あら？ 経絡からもれる
このチャクラの味…。
What?! This taste of Chakra leaking
from your Chakra Network.
キミ 珍しく
風の性質変化を持ってるのね。
So you've got the rare wind
Chakra nature, huh?
だったら 何だってんだよ！
So what if I do?!
私のコレクションになってみない？
How about becoming part
of my collection?
ん… え？
Hm?! Huh?
Do you prefer French or soft?
フレンチとソフト どっちが好み？
はぁ… それ 食いもん？
Are those foods or something?
(フウカ)ったく… 接吻のことよ。
They're kisses.
つまり…！
In other words...
You mean you're going to kiss me?!
チュ… チューするってことか!?
ウフフ… そう うぶな子ね！
Yes.
You're such an inexperienced boy.
ファーストキスは まだなのかしら？
You still haven't even
had your first kiss?
Yikes! What?!
Don't mess with me!
なめんなよ！
オレだって チューぐらい経験あらぁ！
Even I've had experience kissing!
相手は男だったけど…。
It was with a guy, though.
そう まあ どうだっていいわ。
I see. Well, whatever.
How about having lots of fun with me?
これから２人で
たっぷり楽しまない？
冗談じゃねえってばよ！
誰が テメエなんかの相手すっかよ！
Not a chance!
Who'd want anything to do with you?
Oh, my... I've been turned down...
あらやだ… フラれちゃった。
Hey, what's with her?!
なんだよ アイツ！
ああいうタイプは苦手だってばよ！
I'm not good with women like that!
ウフフフ… 女の誘いを
断るなんて いけない子！
You must not turn down a proposition
from a woman, kid!
逃 が さ な い…！
I-won't-let-you-get-away.
No! C-Cut it out!
ダメ！ やめて…！
屍鬼接吻…。
Reaper Kiss.
なにっ…!?
What?!
はずれ！ 残念でした！
You missed! Too bad!
ねえちゃんのチュー
ちょっと冷たかったけど➡
Your kiss was kind of cold, but soft.
やわらかかったってばよ！
Here you could've gone to
the next world comfortably
おとなしくしてりゃ
気持よく あの世にいけたものを！
if you'd just held still...
Well, guess which one of us is real!
さあて どれが本物でしょうか!?
私を怒らせてしまったね！
Now you've made me angry.
(フエン)ホホホ… これはね
幻術なんかじゃない。
This isn't a Genjutsu.
(フエン)私が設計し 作った地形を➡
I summoned the terrain
I designed and created
他の空間から呼び寄せた…。
from a different spatial environment..
(フエン)あなたは もう…➡
You can't escape now.
もう 逃げられない。
(サイ)敵の作ったフィールドで
戦うほど バカじゃない。
I'm not so stupid as to fight in
a field created by the enemy.
フン… 隠れてもムダムダ。
It's useless to hide.
私の目から逃れることは
できないわ。 だって…➡
You'll never be free from my eyes.
After all, you've already
got my mark on you.
あなたには すでに
私の印がつけられてる。
どこへ逃げようと
お見通しってわけ。
I can see right through you
no matter where you try to escape to.
フッ…。
《まいたか？》
Did I lose her?
早く… みんなと合流しないと。
I've got to join up
with the others quick.
フフフ…。
その道を選んだのね。
So you chose that path, huh?
なに!?
ボクの姿は ヤツからは
見えないはず…。
She shouldn't be able to see me.
なぜ 行く先々に 仕掛けが!?
Why?
Why are there traps wherever I go?!
フッ… 遊びは
ここまでに しといてあげる。
I'll bring the playtime
to an end here.
うわっ!?
How unfortunate...
(フエン)残念ね。
あなたの動きは➡
All of your movements appear
on this design drawing.
すべて この設計図の上に
記されているの。
土遁 岩窃棍！
Earth Style: Spears of Stone
とどめよ！
This is the finishing blow!
はっ！
忍法 超獣偽画！
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll
岩窃棍！
Spears of Stone!
逃げちゃったんだ…。
He got away.
…私を コケにするなんて。
I can't believe he made
a fool of me.
まぁ 私に
いっぱい食わせるなんて➡
Well, he might just be
on the right track
やっぱ いい線いってるのかもね。
since he was actually able
to outmaneuver me.
(ダンゾウ)フン！ こんな年寄りを➡
This isn't the time to be
standing guard over an old man.
見張っている場合でもなかろうに。
(シズネ)夜間通信？
A night transmission?!
What's that?
(綱手)何だ それは？
フクロウです。
シマフクロウの一種でしょうか。
It's an owl.
Is it a Blakiston's fish owl?
だからなぜ フクロウがいる！
I want to know what an owl
is doing here!
火ノ寺より 緊急の報せです。
Oh! It's an urgent report from
the Fire Temple.
It seems Team Kakashi,
in pursuit of the grave robbers,
墓荒らしを 追っていた
カカシ班が敵の罠にはまったらしく。
has been caught in an enemy trap.
それを早く言え！
Why didn't you say that sooner?!
１匹は片づけた。
I took care of one of them.
フン 私のはアンタの相手と違って
ちょっとは やる子だったのよ。
Unlike your opponent,
mine was a kid with some fight in him.
逃がしたか。
Did he get away?
ここは
私がつくった 完璧な迷路なの。
This is the perfect labyrinth
I have created.
まず 生きては出られないわ。
There's pretty much
no way to get out alive.
I wonder.
どうだかな。
This is just a precursor
of the traps to come.
まだまだ仕掛けは 序の口。
私の仕掛けから逃げられたら
拍手喝采ってとこかしら。
Maybe I'll give them a round
of applause
if they are able to escape
from my traps.
This smell... It's sulfur.
このにおいは 硫黄？
毒性はなさそうね。
It doesn't seem to be poisonous.
サイ！
Sai!
忍法 超獣偽画！
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll
サイ！
Sai!
サイ 動かないで。
Sai, don't move!
骨が折れてる。
You've got a broken bone.
ちょっと痛いけど 我慢してね。
This is going to hurt a bit,
but tough it out.
(サクラ)これで よしっと！
That should do it!
Now for the spider poison.
(サクラ)次は クモの毒ね。
毒性は弱いから心配ない。
It's of low toxicity,
so you don't need to worry.
すぐ解毒するわ。
I'll neutralize the poison right away.
あの… 感動しましたか？
Umm... were you moved?
Huh?
えっ？
感動したんですね。
You were moved, weren't you?
だから こんなこと。
That's why you're doing this...
What're you talking about?!
なに？ それ。
"Recommendations
for Self-Sacrifice"?!
(サクラ)『自己犠牲の勧め』？
Yes. In order to create better
personal connections,
はい。 人間関係 特に女性と
よりよい関係をつくるためには➡
with women in particular...
我が身を
なげうつことが効果ありだと。
it says it's effective to lay down
your life for someone.
やっぱり 有効なんですね。
ナルト君にもやってみようかな？
Maybe I'll try this with Naruto, too.
What?
はぁ？ いい加減にしろ！
Knock it off!
うあ～っ！
Now that you've made me angry,
your luck has run out, boy.
私を怒らせたのが
運のつきね 坊や。
Now you're serious?!
おう！ 本気になったか？
That's what I want!
望むところだってばよ！
Okay, bring it on.
ちゃっちゃと かかってこい！
Can you kiss all of us at once?
さ～て 全員 いっぺんに
チュウできるかな？
火遁… 鳳仙火の術。
Fire Style: Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
ウフフフ… しょせん 坊やだねぇ。
You're just a boy, after all.
さて 本物は どこに
隠れているのかしら？
Now, I wonder where the real one
is hiding.
やったか？
Did I get her?
なにっ!?
What?!
Damn it! What's going on?
クソッ… どういうことだってばよ。
確かに 手応えは
あったはずなのに…。
And here,
I'm sure I felt like I hit something.
(フウカ)アハハハハハ…。
(フウカ)土遁 岩隠れの術。
Earth Style: Hidden in Stones Jutsu!
ちょっとは やるようね。
It appears you've got
some fight in you.
改めて欲しくなったわ。
キミの風のチャクラ。
Now I want your wind Chakra
even more.
お前… 不死身なのか!?
Are you immortal?
オレの螺旋丸くらって
無傷なんて ありえねえ！
No way can you be unharmed
after getting hit by my Rasengan.
キミの攻撃は まだまだ甘いのよ。
Your attacks are still too soft.
それより 今度こそ
受けてもらうわよ。 死の接吻。
More importantly, this time for sure
you will receive my kiss of death.
うぅ… そう簡単には させねえよ。
I won't let you do that so easily!
まずは その減らず口
たたけないようにしてあげるわ。
First, I'll make it so
you can't talk back.
影分身の術。
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
(フウカ)あらあら 芸がないわね。
また影分身？
Oh, my. No artfulness at all.
More Shadow Clones?
それじゃ こちらは…➡
Then I'll go with...
Water Style! Mouth of the Serpent!
水遁 邪の口。
なんだ？
What?!
《アイツ…
火と土と水のチャクラ性質…》
She has earth, fire and water
Chakra natures.
《３つも持ってやがんのか》
She's got three of them?
雷遁 地走り！
Lighting Style: Earth Flash!
《なに!? 雷だと？
じゃあ ４つものチャクラ性質を…》
What?! Lightning?!
She's got four Chakra natures!
あっ… あぁっ！
(ソラ)あれは いってぇ…。
What the hell is that?!
(ソラ)何者だ？
Who're you?!
(フリド)お前が ソラか…。
会いたかったぞ。
So you're Sora, huh?
I missed you.
kodomo no koro mita niji wo
I look up at the rainbow I saw as a child.
ima miageru to nanairo de wa naku
But the prism colors are gone,
yagate kiri ga kakari
Shrouded in mist instead.
jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
I search for you as you change,
kimi wo sagashite mo doko ni mo inai
With the passage of time but you're nowhere to be found.
me wo toji kokoro hiraite
I close my eyes and open my heart.
mata nagemete mite mo nani mo kawaranai no ka
And stare hard again just to see if nothing really changes.
tashikamete mitai
I need to know.
sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
I make a wish that the mist will clear.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
If I'm true to myself and shout it out.
nanika wo nakushite shimatta koto de sou
Maybe by losing something.
ウッ… アヒィ…。
(トントン)ブゥ。
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
There must be something I gain as well.
(シズネ)ありがとう 大丈夫よ。
(ヤマト)重そうですね。
ヤマト隊長。 どうしました？
dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
But we're still confused about adulthood.
任務報告書を提出しに。
では ここにのせてください。
ikito yuku sube sagashiteru
And searching for the means to live on.
アハハ… 手伝いましょうか？
失礼します。
Next Episode
《まさか 書類が
こんなにあるとは…》
Damn it.
Mysteries of the female body, my foot.
Hair is the most important thing
to a woman, my foot!
えぇ～っ!?
I don't want to know anything
about stuff like that.
こちらの報告書にも
判を お願いしますね。
At any rate, earth, fire, water,
lightning, wind...
シズネ！ ちょっとは休ませな。
ダメです！ このあと
忍者登録書の確認➡
She has all of the Chakra properties.
任務の受け付け 上層部との会議
大名との懇談会 それから…。
But I'll do my best with
my Wind Style.
Now I'll show the fruits
of my training!
(綱手)わかった わかった！
Hey, wait a minute.
火影様の仕事は 激務ですね。
I still haven't learned
any Wind Style Jutsu.
みんな 面倒かけてくれるからな。
Contact
Next time: "Contact"
なかでも やっかいなのが…➡
御意見番のお守りだぁ～！
(シズネ)ウヒィ…。
(ヤマト)ウヒョヒョ…。
Thanks. I'm okay.
Those look heavy.
Oh, Captain Yamato.
What are you doing here?
I came to submit a mission report.
Then please put it here.
Shall I help you?
Excuse me.
I never thought there were
so many documents...
Huh?!
Please put your seal on these reports.
Shizune! Let me rest a little!
No way! After this you have to check
the ninja registration papers,
mission receipts,
a meeting with the brass,
a round-table with a Feudal Lord,
and then...
Okay, okay!
Your work is sure demanding,
isn't it, Hokage-sama?
Because everyone causes me trouble.
And among them, the most troublesome is...
attending to the advisors!
— Yikes!
— Yikes.